

Juan Cereigido.

+54 9 11 6705-7531 juancereigido@outlook.com Buenos Aires, Argentina 🖾



in linkedin/juancereigido



@juancereigido

Hobbies



Film & edit videos



Design and print 3D objects that improve my daily life

Education



Escuela ténica Nº 28 D.E. 10 Electronic technician - 2017



CoderHouse Product Manager



Plataforma 5 Front-end web developer



International Baccalaureate



Brother - Escuela de creativos Summer Creative School

About me

I'm a person who really enjoys when using a product that speaks for itself, and it says that has been made by people who love what they do. That's why I've always had the ambition to be part of a team, that throughout their creations, generates this in the largest number of people possible.

Experience



Pickabox

Product Lead (April 2021 - Present)

- NPS from -13 to 28 in 4 months
- Developed the UI Kit in Figma in order to create an scalable component system

I work every day for creating a better experience for the 10k+ active users that Pickabox has in LATAM for making their purchases in USA or China, coordinating dev, design, operations, and performance marketing in order to grow our KPI's. Take a look at our website!



Holovox

Product Lead & Co-Founder (April 2019 - March 2021)

- Launched functional MVP in 5 weeks
- Led Design Sprints
- Before pivoting to SaaS, I led a growth hacking team for USA & Argentina clients

I started working in the company as an employee, and two years later, who were my bosses offered me to associate in order to put my vision in practice, and led the product team 💅



Orvibo Argentina

Web developer (June 2018 - April 2019)

- Designed and developed the brand's website and interactive landings for new produc
- Produced content (Filmmaking and graphic design) for social media & ads.

My first experience in the tech industry. The business was all about selling imported smart-home products. Although global brands gave us the resources, I worked on devel interactive experiences with landing pages. (It's stills online! 🅯 **Website**)



GÜÜD Lamps

Founder (Noviembre 2016 - Diciembre 2017)

- Launched my first product at the age of 17, making usage of my electronics and design knowledge.
- Designed 3D models for CNC
- Developed and manufactured the PCB that read the sensors and controlled the LED int

One of the best experiences I've lived starting a company. I've failed to sell the second lo products to a local store, and that was the moment I realized I first needed to learn how 😂. The website is no longer online, but I still keep its **Instagram** with love.